(Howard:)What are you talking about?
(Howard:)Remember last week,
when I asked you
(Howard:)if you were wearing Spanx
and you weren't?
(Howard:)How's that different?
(Bernadette:)Maybe you could try being
more thoughtful,
(Bernadette:)like your friend Raj.
(Howard:)Yeah, well, maybe you could
try being more like Raj.
(Bernadette:)-Oh, really?
-Yeah, yeah.
(Howard:)He packed me
a lunch this morning.
(Howard:)And there was a note inside
that said, "Go get them."
(Bernadette:)Like I don't do enough around here.
(Bernadette:)Now I need to pack your lunch?
(Bernadette:)And by the way, why do you need
a note telling you
to go get them?
You're a grown man!
You should know to "go get them!"
I do know to "go get them,"
(Howard:)but sometimes
it's nice to have emotional support
when I'm going and getting them!
(Raj:)Hey, hey, do you hear yourselves?
(Raj:)Let's just, you know, all calm down
and take a step back.
(Bernadette:)This is stupid.
Why are we fighting?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Howard:)I guess I was just feeling
like I'm a lousy husband.
(Bernadette:)You're not a lousy husband.
(Raj:)You're a great husband.
(Bernadette:)I was the one feeling
like a lousy wife.
(Howard:)Are you kidding?
You're the best.
(Howard:)I know what the problem is.
It's him!